luckysmarket.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy | Luckys Market

Hello! Thank you for visiting our Privacy Policy page. Most websites have privacy policies, so we thought it might not be a bad idea to share how fervently we protect your privacy, too. Because we do. We like you. We really, really like you.

So, that said, this Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Lucky’s Market collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.luckysmarket.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Lucky’s Market. So let’s dig into what all of this means, shall we?

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our spectacular site, subscribe to our fantastic newsletter, fill out a snazzy form, and in connection with other awesome activities, super services, fab features or rocking resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, names and email addresses. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously, too, just like a ninja. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. How we doing so far?

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. (We like healthy food, but we like cookies, too! Okay, so not the same kind of cookies…) User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them (not in a creepy way). User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent (cookies taste delicious with milk). If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. That could be a bummer!

### How we use collected information

Lucky’s Market may collect and use Users personal information for the following reasons which have nothing to do with bacon:  
\- **To improve customer service** : Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. We want to help you as quickly as we can so you can go on being your snazzy selves.  
\- **To personalize user experience** : We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. We hope this also makes the site more user friendly. We like friendly.  
\- **To improve our Site** : We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. We love to be even better, so this another way we hope to exceed expectations.  
\- **To send periodic emails** : We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site. We’re cool like that.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. In other words, we protect your information as fervently as we would our own kids (not the goat kind, though we’d protect their privacy, too).

### Sharing your personal information

As with our quality meats, this is where we go all Never Ever: We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. Other than that, it ain’t happening. Your privacy is just too important to us.

### Changes to this privacy policy

We’re with what’s happening now, so Lucky’s Market has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time to make improvements. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. It’s like the law! Only not the law.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you are basically saying you agree with all of this stuff and agree with this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, that’s okay, too; but it would mean that you shouldn’t use this site–and that would make us very sad. You see, we like you and we’ve been together throughout this long missive, so we can weather this, too. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. It’s a little like a friendly handshake. Or a non-creepy hug.

### Contacting us

Do you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, want to talk about bacon or your dealings with this site? Please contact us at:

### Lucky’s Market

Lucky’s Market, LLC 6328 Monarch Park Place, Suite 100 Niwot, CO 80503  
This document was last updated on April 2, 2014
